profitmoffatt.com 2016-06-01

# Profit Moffatt Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy**

Jason Moffatt Inc is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to keep you informed about new updates from the site, to process orders and to provide support for our products. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.

**How does Jason Moffatt Inc. protect customer information?**

We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the Internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

**What about “cookies”?**

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.

**Will Jason Moffatt Inc. disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Jason Moffatt Inc. does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Jason Moffatt Inc. may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Jason Moffatt Inc. may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Jason Moffatt Inc., our users, or others.

**In Summary**

Jason Moffatt Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at NicheFamous.com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Jason Moffatt Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Jason Moffatt Inc. also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Jason Moffatt Inc. has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Jason Moffatt Inc. and cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

**Questions and Feedback**

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at profitmoffatthelp@gmail.com

Sincerely,

Jason Moffatt
